Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXVI is arranged in 23 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXVI. CANADIAN LABOUR CONGRESS / TRADES AND LABOUR CONGRESS OF CANADA
  - Sub-Series 273-0. Canadian Labour Congress and Trades and Labour Congress of Canada
    - General, 1964 (Box 252, Folder 20)
    - General, 1960-1963 (Box 252, Folder 21)
    - General, 1956-1959 (Box 252, Folder 22)
    - General, 1949-1955 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      August 21, 1949-55.
    - General, 1949 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      April 9, 1949-August 20, 1949.
    - General, 1949 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      January 1949-April 8, 1949.
    - General, 1921-1948 (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 273-1. TLC
    - Per Capita Tax -1921-1953 (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 273-2. TLC
    - Affiliations, 1921-1951 (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 273-3. TLC
    - Financial Assistance, 1921 (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 273-4. Canadian Labour Congress
    - 1956-1963 (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Trades and Labour Congress of Canada (TLC). Convention, 1922 (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 273-5. TLC
    - Convention, 1923 (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 273-6. TLC
    - Convention Delegates, 1923 (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 273-7. TLC
    - Convention Report, 1924 (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 273-8. TLC
    - Canadian Congress Journal, 1924-1927 (Box 253, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 273-9. TLC
    - Convention, 1925 (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 273-10. TLC
    - Convention, 1926 (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 273-11. TLC
    - Dual Organizations, 1926 (Box 253, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 273-12. TLC
    - Convention, 1927 (Box 253, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 273-14. TLC
    - Convention, 1929 (Box 253, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 273-15. TLC
    - Convention, 1930 (Box 253, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 273-16. TLC
    - Political Program, 1930-1957 (Box 253, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 273-17. TLC
    - Convention, 1931 (Box 253, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 273-18. TLC
    - Convention, 1932 (Box 253, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 273-19. TLC
    - Convention, 1933 (Box 253, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 273-20. TLC
    - Convention, 1934 (Box 253, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 273-21. TLC
    - Convention, 1935 (Box 253, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 273-22. TLC
    - Convention, 1936 (Box 253, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 273-23. TLC
    - Conventions, 1949-1955 (Box 253, Folder 27)
      October 1949-55.
    - Conventions, 1937-1949 (Box 253, Folder 28)
      1937-September 1949.